<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
		<title>Dow Jones News</title>
		<link>https://dow-jones.com/</link>
		<description>Dow Jones News.</description>
		<language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Interbank Foreign Exchange Rates At 00:50 EST / 0550 GMT]]></title>
      <pubDate>2022-01-19T05:50:19.819</pubDate>
      <guid>20220119000071</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>
 
                           Latest       Previous   %Chg    Daily    Daily   %Chg 
Dollar Rates                               Close            High      Low  12/31 
 
USD/JPY Japan           114.22-23      114.58-59  -0.32   114.78   114.22  -0.77 
EUR/USD Euro            1.1327-30      1.1326-29  +0.01   1.1335   1.1319  -0.39 
GBP/USD U.K.            1.3605-07      1.3595-97  +0.07   1.3611   1.3588  +0.58 
USD/CHF Switzerland     0.9155-59      0.9172-76  -0.19   0.9179   0.9157  +0.37 
USD/CAD Canada          1.2502-07      1.2511-16  -0.07   1.2520   1.2487  -1.08 
AUD/USD Australia       0.7185-89      0.7182-86  +0.04   0.7197   0.7177  -1.07 
NZD/USD New Zealand     0.6784-90      0.6766-72  +0.27   0.6791   0.6764  -0.76 
 
Euro Rates 
 
EUR/JPY Japan           129.37-42      129.77-81  -0.30   130.01   129.39  -1.16 
EUR/GBP U.K.            0.8326-29      0.8329-32  -0.04   0.8336   0.8324  -0.96 
EUR/CHF Switzerland     1.0374-77      1.0393-96  -0.18   1.0396   1.0376  +0.06 
EUR/CAD Canada          1.4161-71      1.4168-78  -0.05   1.4179   1.4139  -1.43 
EUR/AUD Australia       1.5758-68      1.5762-72  -0.03   1.5780   1.5740  +0.75 
EUR/DKK Denmark         7.4357-64      7.4357-64   0.00   7.4361   7.4361   0.00 
EUR/NOK Norway          9.9719-69      9.9729-79  -0.01   9.9946   9.9609  -0.50 
EUR/SEK Sweden        10.3538-638    10.3445-545  +0.09  10.3754  10.3411  +0.68 
EUR/CZK Czech Rep.     24.383-413     24.372-402  +0.05   24.417   24.367  -2.09 
EUR/HUF Hungary       357.83-8.23    357.62-8.02  +0.06   358.30   357.47  -3.00 
EUR/PLN Poland         4.5332-428     4.5278-374  +0.12   4.5469   4.5301  -1.12 
 
Yen Rates 
 
AUD/JPY Australia        82.08-12       82.30-34  -0.27    82.54    82.09  -1.85 
GBP/JPY U.K.            155.38-44      155.74-80  -0.23   156.08   155.41  -0.16 
CAD/JPY Canada           91.32-37       91.55-59  -0.25    91.86    91.34  +0.29 
NZD/JPY New Zealand      77.48-56       77.56-60  -0.08    77.83    77.51  -1.55 
 
Other Dollar Rates 
 
USD/CZK Czech Rep.      21.510-60      21.500-50  +0.05   21.566   21.482  -1.56 
USD/HUF Hungary       315.83-6.23    315.69-6.09  +0.04   316.25   315.69  -2.66 
USD/DKK Denmark         6.5689-99     6.5697-707  -0.01   6.5756   6.5663  +0.44 
USD/NOK Norway          8.8014-74      8.8026-86  -0.01   8.8263   8.7958  -0.03 
USD/PLN Poland          4.0014-89      3.9977-04  +0.09   4.0146   4.0012  -0.57 
USD/RUB Russia         77.083-153      76.998-07  +0.11   77.152   76.844  +3.11 
USD/SEK Sweden         9.1387-477     9.1329-419  +0.06   9.1559   9.1281  +1.00 
USD/ZAR S. Africa     15.5133-433    15.5007-307  +0.08  15.5365  15.4841  -2.60 
 
USD/CNY China          6.3489-509      6.3520-40  -0.05   6.3557   6.3495  -0.09 
USD/HKD Hong Kong       7.7917-22      7.7918-23   0.00   7.7933   7.7901  -0.06 
USD/MYR Malaysia       4.1893-943      4.1810-60  +0.20   4.1955   4.1835  +0.62 
USD/INR India           74.610-20      74.615-16   0.00   74.835   74.564  +0.14 
USD/IDR Indonesia        14357-71       14331-45  +0.18    14378    14338  +0.78 
USD/PHP Philippines     51.430-60      51.464-84  -0.06   51.600   51.430  +0.87 
USD/SGD Singapore      1.3497-507      1.3503-13  -0.04   1.3516   1.3498  +0.12 
USD/KRW S. Korea     1191.06-3.06   1192.03-4.03  -0.08  1193.96  1190.71  +0.27 
USD/TWD Taiwan          27.615-45     27.579-609  +0.13   27.653   27.531  -0.31 
USD/THB Thailand       33.180-200      33.070-90  +0.33   33.250   33.090  -0.12 
USD/VND Vietnam          22729-32       22759-62  -0.13    22760    22730  -0.55 
 
USD/BRL Brazil          5.5654-84      5.5656-86   0.00   5.5678   5.5659  -0.08 
USD/MXN Mexico        20.4006-306   20.3884-4184  +0.06  20.4205  20.3815  -0.42 
USD/ARS Argentina    104.1158-810  104.0974-1626  +0.02 104.1668 104.0749  +1.43 
 
Source: Tullett Prebon 
 </p>
<p>
  (END) Dow Jones Newswires</p>
<p>
  January 19, 2022 00:50 ET (05:50 GMT)</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Press Release: ASML reports EUR18.6 billion net sales and EUR5.9 billion net income in 2021]]></title>
      <pubDate>2022-01-19T06:00:01.292</pubDate>
      <guid>20220119000100</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>
  ASML reports EUR18.6 billion net sales and EUR5.9 billion net income in 2021 </p>
<p>
  ASML reports EUR18.6 billion net sales and EUR5.9 billion net income in 2021 </p>
<p>
  Sales growth of around 20% expected for 2022 </p>
<p>
  VELDHOVEN, the Netherlands, January 19, 2022 -- today ASML Holding NV (ASML) has published its 2021 fourth-quarter and full-year results. </p>
<p>
   -- Q4 net sales of EUR5.0 billion, gross margin of 54.2%, net income of 
      EUR1.8 billion 
 
   -- Q4 net bookings of EUR7.1 billion2 
 
   -- 2021 net sales of EUR18.6 billion, gross margin of 52.7%, net income of 
      EUR5.9 billion 
 
   -- ASML expects Q1 2022 net sales between EUR3.3 billion and EUR3.5 billion 
      and a gross margin of around 49% 
 
   -- Approximately EUR2 billion worth of sales that are expected to ship in 
      the first quarter are not included in this number, and will be recognized 
      in subsequent quarters after formal customer acceptance tests are 
      completed in the field 
 
   -- ASML expects 2022 net sales to grow around 20% compared to 2021. The 
      expected impact of the fire in part of a building at our Berlin site is 
      included in this. Based on our current insights, we believe we can manage 
      the consequences of this fire without significant impact on our system 
      output for 2022 
 
   -- ASML intends to declare a total dividend over 2021 of EUR5.50 per 
      ordinary share (100% increase compared to previous year) 
 
(Figures in millions 
of euros unless 
otherwise indicated)     Q3 2021       Q4 2021        FY 2020       FY 2021 
---------------------  ------------  ------------  -------------  ------------ 
Net sales                     5,241         4,986         13,979        18,611 
...of which Installed 
 Base Management 
 sales (1)                    1,130         1,522          3,662         4,958 
 
New lithography 
 systems sold 
 (units)                         72            72            236           286 
Used lithography 
 systems sold 
 (units)                          7            10             22            23 
 
Net bookings (2)              6,179         7,050         11,292        26,240 
 
Gross profit                  2,711         2,701          6,798         9,809 
Gross margin (%)               51.7          54.2           48.6          52.7 
 
Net income                    1,740         1,774          3,554         5,883 
EPS (basic; in euros)          4.27          4.39           8.49         14.36 
 
End-quarter cash and 
 cash equivalents and 
 short-term 
 investments                  4,456         7,590          7,351         7,590 
                       ------------  ------------  -------------  ------------ 
 </p>
<p>
  (1) Installed Base Management sales equals our net service and field option sales. </p>
<p>
  (2) Our systems net bookings include all system sales orders for which written authorizations have been accepted. As of Q4 2021 and for FY 2021, this includes EUV 0.55 NA (High-NA) systems. We have not restated comparable periods for previously received EUV 0.55 NA (High-NA) sales orders. </p>
<p>
  Numbers have been rounded for readers&apos; convenience. A complete summary of US GAAP Consolidated Statements of Operations is published on www.asml.com </p>
<p>
  CEO statement and outlook </p>
<p>
  &quot;Our fourth-quarter net sales came in at EUR5.0 billion which is within our guidance. The gross margin of 54.2%, is higher than guided due to strong Installed Base revenue. Our fourth-quarter net bookings came in at EUR7.1 billion, including EUR2.6 billion from 0.33 NA and 0.55 NA EUV systems. </p>
<p>
  &quot;The total net sales for the year was EUR18.6 billion, including EUR6.3 billion from 42 EUV systems. For ASML, 2021 was a strong growth year in a dynamic environment. </p>
<p>
  &quot;We experience higher demand for our systems than our production capacity can accommodate. Very strong demand in end markets puts pressure on our customers for more wafer output. In order to support our customers, we are providing them with high-productivity upgrade solutions for their installed base, and we are reducing cycle time in our factory to ship more systems. One way to reduce cycle time is through a fast shipment process that skips some of the testing in our factory. Final testing and formal acceptance then takes place at the customer site. This leads to a deferral of revenue recognition for those shipments until formal customer acceptance, but does provide our customers with earlier access to wafer output capacity. </p>
<p>
  &quot;ASML expects first-quarter net sales between EUR3.3 billion and EUR3.5 billion with a gross margin of around 49%. ASML expects R&amp;D costs of around EUR760 million and SG&amp;A costs of around EUR210 million. The lower net sales guidance for the first quarter is due to a significant number of fast shipments, translating to approximately EUR2 billion of expected revenue shift from the first quarter to subsequent quarters. Looking at the full year -- even taking into account our current expectation of fast-shipment-related revenue shifts of six EUV systems into 2023 -- we expect a revenue growth of around 20%,&quot; said ASML President and Chief Executive Officer Peter Wennink. </p>
<p>
  Products and business highlights </p>
<p>
   -- In our EUV business, we received one order for the TWINSCAN EXE:5000 in 
      the fourth quarter. We already received four orders in 2018. </p>
<p>
  Early 2022, we received the first order for the next generation, TWINSCAN EXE:5200, marking the next step on the path to 0.55 NA EUV introduction. </p>
<p>
   -- In our DUV business, the XT:860N was shipped to its first customer at the 
      end of 2021. This KrF system offers improved performance and a lower cost 
      per exposure. </p>
<p>
  In 2022 we will add KrF to the NXT platform with the introduction of the NXT:870, allowing us to make a significant step in productivity and cost of ownership, building on the existing experience on this platform in ArFi and ArF dry. </p>
<p>
   -- In our Applications business, shipment of the first eScan1100 multibeam 
      inspection system designed for high-volume manufacturing is planned in 
      the coming weeks. With 25 beams (5x5), we expect the eScan1100 to 
      increase throughput up to 15 times compared to single e-beam inspection 
      tools for targeted in-line defect inspection applications. </p>
<p>
  Dividend proposal and share buyback program update </p>
<p>
  ASML intends to declare a total dividend in respect of 2021 of EUR5.50 per ordinary share. Recognizing the interim dividend of EUR1.80 per ordinary share paid in November 2021, this leads to a final dividend proposal to the General Meeting of EUR3.70 per ordinary share. The total 2021 dividend is a 100% increase compared to the 2020 total dividend of EUR2.75 per ordinary share. </p>
<p>
  As part of its financial policy to return excess cash to its shareholders through growing annualized dividends and regularly timed share buybacks, ASML executes a share buyback program which started on July 22, 2021, and is to be closed by December 31, 2023. As part of this program, ASML intends to repurchase shares up to an amount of EUR9 billion, of which we expect a total of up to 0.45 million shares will be used to cover employee share plans. ASML intends to cancel the remainder of the shares repurchased. In the fourth quarter, we purchased around EUR2.5 billion of shares under the current program. </p>
<p>
  The share buyback program will be executed within the limitations of the existing authority granted by the Annual General Meeting of Shareholders (AGM) on April 29, 2021, and of the authority to be granted by future AGMs. The share buyback program may be suspended, modified or discontinued at any time. All transactions under this program will be published on ASML&apos;s website (www.asml.com/investors) on a weekly basis. </p>
<p>
 
Media Relations contacts        Investor Relations contacts 
Monique Mols +31 6 5284 4418    Skip Miller +1 480 235 0934 
Brittney Wolff Zatezalo +1 408  Marcel Kemp +31 40 268 6494 
 483 3207 
Karen Lo +886 36 23 6639        Peter Cheang +886 3 659 6771 
 </p>
<p>
  Quarterly video interview, press conference and investor call </p>
<p>
  With this press release, ASML has published a video interview in which CEO Peter Wennink discusses the 2021 fourth-quarter and full-year results and outlook for 2022. This video and the transcript can be viewed on www.asml.com. </p>
<p>
  CEO Peter Wennink and CFO Roger Dassen will host a virtual press conference in Veldhoven on January 19, 2022, at 11:00 Central European Time, which will be accessible via live webcast on www.asml.com. </p>
<p>
  An investor call for both investors and the media will be hosted by CEO Peter Wennink and CFO Roger Dassen on January 19, 2022 at 15:00 Central European Time / 09:00 US Eastern Time. Details can be found on our website. </p>
<p>
  About ASML </p>
<p>
  ASML is a leading supplier to the semiconductor industry. The company provides chipmakers with hardware, software and services to mass produce the patterns of integrated circuits (microchips). Together with its partners, ASML drives the advancement of more affordable, more powerful, more energy-efficient microchips. ASML enables groundbreaking technology to solve some of humanity&apos;s toughest challenges, such as in healthcare, energy use and conservation, mobility and agriculture. ASML is a multinational company headquartered in Veldhoven, the Netherlands, with offices across Europe, the US and Asia. Every day, ASML&apos;s more than 32,000 employees (FTE) challenge the status quo and push technology to new limits. ASML is traded on Euronext Amsterdam and NASDAQ under the symbol ASML. Discover ASML -- our products, technology and career opportunities -- at www.asml.com. </p>
<p>
  US GAAP and IFRS Financial Reporting </p>
<p>
  ASML&apos;s primary accounting standard for quarterly earnings releases and annual reports is US GAAP, the accounting principles generally accepted in the United States of America. Quarterly US GAAP consolidated statements of operations, consolidated statements of cash flows and consolidated balance sheets are available on www.asml.com. </p>
<p>
  (MORE TO FOLLOW) Dow Jones Newswires</p>
<p>
  January 19, 2022 01:00 ET (06:00 GMT)</p>
]]>
      </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
