<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
		<title>Trading Economics News</title>
		<link>https://tradingeconomics.com/</link>
		<description>Trading Economics News.</description>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 08:24:42 +0100</lastBuildDate>
		<language>en</language>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[UK Stocks Edge Down for 2nd Session]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/united-kingdom/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T07:27:00</pubDate>
      <guid>350239</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The FTSE 100 traded marginally lower on Tuesday, following a 0.1% loss in the previous session, as geopolitical tensions between the US and China offset upbeat results from oil major BP. US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi will allegedly visit Taiwan today and China has warned of \"serious consequences\" if the trip goes ahead. On the corporate front, BP profits topped forecasts amid rising commodity prices while the oil giant also announced a 10% increase in its quarterly dividend payout; and Sage said it expects full-year revenue growth at the top end of forecasts.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[China Stocks Sink as Sino-US Tensions Rise]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/china/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T07:27:36.057</pubDate>
      <guid>350238</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The Shanghai Composite sank 2.26% to 3,186 while the Shenzhen Component lost 2.37% to 12,120 on Tuesday, closing at their lowest levels in at least a month, as escalating tensions between China and the US ahead of US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s expected visit to Taiwan sparked a broad selloff in Asia. Investor sentiment was also weighed down by mounting risk of a global recession as weak manufacturing data in major economies highlighted the darkening economic outlook. High-growth technology and new energy stocks led the market selloff, with sharp losses from East Money Information (-2.6%), Luxshare Precision (-3.5%), TCL Zhonghuan (-2.5%), Contemporary Amperex (-2.1%), Tianqi Lithium (-4.9%) and Longi Green Energy (-2.7%). All other sectors in China declined, including heavyweight consumer, industrial and financial names.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Japanese Shares Drop in Broad Decline]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/japan/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:51:26.857</pubDate>
      <guid>350231</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The Nikkei 225 Index dropped 1.42% to 27,595 while the Topix Index lost 1.77% to 1,925 on Tuesday, retreating from two-month closing highs, with all sectors finishing in negative territory as a stronger yen, mixed corporate earnings and the risk of a global recession dented sentiment. Investors were also kept on edge by fears of an escalation in Sino-US tensions as US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi is set to visit Taiwan despite objections from China. Technology firms led the market selloff, with notable losses from SoftBank Group (-1%), Tokyo Electron (-2%), Keyence (-1.6%), Murata Manufacturing (-1.3%), Recruit Holdings (-2%) and Mercari Inc (-4.1%). Other index heavyweights also declined, including Sony Group (-0.8%), Mitsubishi Corp (-1.6%), Toyota (-2.6%), Nintendo (-1.9%) and Mitsui & Co (-4%).</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[UK Shares to Open Lower]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/united-kingdom/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:49:55.763</pubDate>
      <guid>350230</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>Contracts on the FTSE 100 futures were down 0.6% on Tuesday, tracking global negative cues, amid geopolitical tensions between the US and China. US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi will allegedly visit Taiwan today and China has warned of \"serious consequences\" if the trip goes ahead. Meanwhile, concerns about the strength of the global economy linger and the earnings season continues. BP profit topping forecasts amid rising commodity prices while the oil giant also announced a 10% increase in its quarterly dividend payout. Sage said it expects full year revenue growth at the top end of forecasts.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[New Zealand Stocks Close Slightly Higher]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/new-zealand/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:43:00</pubDate>
      <guid>350229</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The NZX 50 was up 6.56 points or less than 0.1% to finish at 11,532.46 on Tuesday, up for the fourth session while staying at its highest close in near three months. Sentiment continued to be supported by news that New Zealand's borders are fully open for the first time since March 2020, when they shut in an effort to keep out COVID-19. Traders tried to shrug off a drop on Wall Street overnight as well as an escalation in Sino-US tensions as US House of Representatives Speaker Nancy Pelosi is set to begin a visit to Taiwan today against the objections of China. The A2 Milk Company jumped near 9%, as the company may get approval as soon as this week on its application to sell its baby formula in the US. Other gainers were Plexure Group (26.2%), Pacific Edge Limited (11.3%), and Oceania Healthcare (4.1%), while among decliners were New Talisman Gold Mines (-33.3%), NZ Automotive Investments (-12.5%), Greenfern Industries (-7.5%), and Third Age Health Services (-7.2%).</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Australian Shares Inch Up After RBA Decision]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/australia/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:32:00</pubDate>
      <guid>350228</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The S&P/ASX 200 Index rose slightly by 0.07% to 6,998 on Tuesday, closing at its highest level in over seven weeks, after the Reserve Bank of Australia lifted the cash rate in a widely expected move and tempered guidance on future hikes amid expectations of a slowdown in the economy. RBA Governor Philip Lowe also said that there was no pre-set path to policy, in contrast to his previous, more hawkish statements that the central bank was intent on bringing interest rates to a “neutral” level of at least 2.5%. Technology stocks led the market, with notable gains from Xero Ltd (1.1%), Wisetech Global (1%) and Block Inc (2.7%). Financial shares also advanced, with the “Big Four” banks rising between 0.3% to 1.6%. Meanwhile, energy and mining stocks fell on weaker commodity prices. Artificial intelligence firm Appen Ltd also slumped 27.3% after saying it expected to post its first half-year loss since becoming a public company amid a weak digital ad environment and rising costs.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[European Stocks to Open Lower, US-China Tensions in Focus]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/germany/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:30:00</pubDate>
      <guid>350227</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>European futures were lower on Tuesday, with contracts on both the Dax and Stoxx 50 futures losing nearly 0.7% each, and tracking its Asian peers lower. Geopolitical tensions between the US and China weighed on investors mood amid news that House Speaker Nancy Pelosi will visit Taiwan today. China has warned of "serious consequences" if the trip goes ahead. At the same time, traders continue to follow economic data for any signs of a potential recession while keeping a close eye on earnings. BP profit topped forecasts amid rising commodity prices and the company announced  a 10% increase in its quarterly dividend payout.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[The Nikkei 225 Index decreased 1.36%]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/japan/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T06:30:05.913</pubDate>
      <guid>350226</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>In Tokyo the Nikkei 225 Index decreased 380 points or 1.36 percent on Tuesday. Losses were driven by Hino Motors, (-9.32%), Isetan Mitsukoshi (-5.26%) and Toto (-4.87%).</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Sensex Falls for 1st Time in 5 Sessions]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/india/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T05:44:00</pubDate>
      <guid>350217</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The BSE Sensex dropped 226.2 points or 0.39% to 57,890 in morning deals on Tuesday, down for the first session in five and tracking a pullback in Asian markets following a drop on Wall Street overnight, due to fears that an aggressive tightening from the Fed will eventually lead to a global recession. Traders were also wary of escalating US-China tensions ahead of a possible trip by US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi to Taiwan today. Locally, the RBI will announce its monetary policy decision Friday, with markets expecting a further rate hike as India's inflation runs at a near-decade high and the rupee is trading near a record low. Metal and IT stocks led the decline, amid sharp losses from Hindalco Industries (-3.17%), Welspun Corp (-2.87%), Jindal Steel (-2.6%), Tata Steel (-1.4%), and Tech Mahindra (-1.2%). By contrast, ITC surged nearly 3%, after posting a 33.46% yoy rise in its April-June net profit. Shares of SBI also moved higher (1.9%), as did Bajaj Finance (0.3%).</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[China Stocks Sink as Sino-US Tensions Grow]]></title>
      <link>https://tradingeconomics.com/china/stock-market</link>
      <pubDate>2022-08-02T03:41:16.187</pubDate>
      <guid>350211</guid>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[<p>The Shanghai Composite sank 3% to 3,162 while the Shenzhen Component lost 2.6% to 12,080 on Tuesday, hitting their lowest levels in about two months, as growing tensions between China and the US ahead of US House Speaker Nancy Pelosi’s expected visit to Taiwan sparked a broad selloff in Asia. Investor sentiment has also been dampened by the risk of a global recession as weak manufacturing data in major economies highlighted the darkening global economic outlook. High-growth technology and new energy stocks led the decline, with sharp losses from East Money Information (-3.5%), Luxshare Precision (-3.5%), Han’s Laser Technology (-4.4%), Contemporary Amperex (-2.4%), Tianqi Lithium (-4.3%) and Longi Green Energy (-4.3%). All other sectors in China declined, including heavyweight consumer, industrial and financial names.</p>]]>
      </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
